Arts and Sciences, College of; Records ua600
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
College of Arts and Sciences Records
1955-1977
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
ua600
48.9 cubic ft.
The collection consists of inactive records from the University at Albany's College of Arts and Sciences.
Collection X
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Web Archives
Biographical History
The University at Albany's created the School of Arts and Sciences in 1963 to bring together all the programs in the arts and sciences, in 1964 its name was changed to the College of Arts and Sciences. The College of Arts and Sciences was dissolved in 1978-79 into the new Colleges of Humanities and Fine Arts, Science and Mathematics, and Social and Behavioral Sciences. The College of Arts and Sciences was officially recreated in October of 1993 after the recommendations made by a Task Force on Campus Organization were accepted by then President H. Patrick Swygert. The Colleges of Social and Behavioral Sciences, Science and Mathematics, and Humanities and Fine Arts, were officially brought together to form the College of Arts and Sciences.
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of inactive records of University at Albany's College of Arts and Sciences and documents the administration of the College and the departments within it. Most of the materials predate the re-establishment of the College of Arts and Sciences in 1993. Collection includes annual reports, 1968-76; dean's correspondence with divisions and departments; proposals for new courses and changes for existing ones, 1965-67; Arts and Sciences Council, Executive Committee, and Committee Meeting minutes, 1968-76; Chairmen's Meeting minutes, 1972-73; departmental program evaluations, three- and five-year plans.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged into 8 series: Series 1: College of Arts and Sciences Website Series 2: College of Arts and Sciences Series 3: Self-Studies and Middle States Accreditation Series 4: College of Humanities and Fine Arts Series 5: College of Sciences and Mathematics Series 6: College of Social and Behavioral Sciences Series 7: Center for the Humanities Advisory Board Series 8: College of Arts and Sciences Ad Hoc Committee on Harassment
Immediate Source of Acquisition
All items in this manuscript group were transferred to the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives.
Access
Access to this collection is restricted because it is unprocessed. Portions of the collection may contain recent administrative records and/or personally identifiable information. While it is likely that portions of the collection may be viewed, access must be managed by an archivist.
Web Archives; UAlbany Schools & Colleges; State University of New York at Albany. College of Arts and Sciences
- College of Arts & Sciences Website, 1
  URL
  http://www.albany.edu/cas/
  Web Collection
- College of Arts and Sciences, 1955-1995; 2; 18.4 cubic ft.
  Scope and Contents
  This series is made up of materials from the first incarnation of the College of Arts and Sciences (CAS), before its split into the College of Fine Arts and Humanities, College of Social and Behavioral Sciences and College of Science and Mathematics. During the period covered by this series, the functions of those colleges were administered by Divisions along similar organizational lines. This series contains some materials that both predate the organization of CAS as well as other materials from after it was subdivided. The bulk of the materials however focus on the college's administration and the various committees that the College of Arts and Sciences Deans L. Gray Cowan and Charles Colman served on during the 1960s and 1970s.
  Series includes divisional and departmental annual reports, correspondence, graduate and undergraduate program reviews, degree and course proposals, memoranda, enrollment data, course listings, committee memberships lists and meeting minutes and budget materials.
  Arrangement
  Series was maintained in the original order after it was transferred.
  - Budget Submitted Request, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Budget Analyses for SUNYA, 1971 March (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Financial Budget, 1969-1972 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Departmental Allocations, 1969 February 2 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Annual Report Humanities, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Annual Report Math and Science, 1969-1971 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Budget Math and Science, 1967-1969 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Annual Report Social Sciences, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - The Research Foundation of the State University of NY, 1966-1969 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Summer Session, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - President Benezet, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Vice President Sirotkin, 1971 November 19 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Vice President Hartley, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Business Office John Hebert, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Educational Communications, 1969-1971 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Office of Institutional, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - A&S Staff Line Allocations, 1968-1970 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - A&S Bulletin, 1968-1970 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Commencement, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Dean of the Humanities, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Dean of Natural Sciences, 1968-1971 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Dean of Social and Behavioral Sciences, 1967-1971 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Interdisciplinary Studies, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - INACTIVE Faculty, undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Humanities Building Space Committee, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Faculty Review Panel, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Curriculum Committee Membership, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Cross Listed Courses, undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Council College Of Arts and Sciences, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - By-Laws, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Bulletin, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Allocations, Department Social and Behavioral Sciences, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Allocations, Department Division of Science/Math, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Allocations, Department Humanities, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Allocations, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Administration, 1966-1971 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Undergraduate Affairs Committee Membership, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Undergraduate Affairs Committee, 1968-1970 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Center For Study Of Sciences And Society, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Conversations In Disciplines, 1966-1969 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Prominent/Gifted Faculty Survey, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Chancellors Office, 1966-1969 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Toll Committee, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Student Participation, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Academic Transfer Students, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Two Year Community College Teacher Preparation, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - University College, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - The State Education Department, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Student Enrollment Projection, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Physical Education, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Teacher Education Programs, 1967-1971 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Strike, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Discretionary Increments Faculty, 1972 June (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Search For Associate Dean Social Sciences, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Search Committee Geology, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Romance Languages Headship, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Move To Mohawk Tower, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Meetings, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Interdisciplinary Major summer, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - History Chairmanship Fall, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Harvard Conference, 1972 May 18-1972 May 19 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Social Science Division Memoranda, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - College of Arts and Sciences Executive Committee, 1966 November-1969 August (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - History File, 1965 October-1970 August (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1964-1969 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Paul Ward Correspondence, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - College of Arts and Sciences, 1967-1968; 1971 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Chairmans Meeting, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Interdisciplinary Studies Program Proposals, 1970-1973 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Student Fellowships Grants, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Curriculum Committee Arts and Services, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Meetings, 1964 December 7 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Eastern European Area Studies Committee, 1969 April 9 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - College of Arts and Sciences, 1967 January (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Committee on Academic Programs, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - By-Laws, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Committee Memoranda, 1968-1974 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Policies Procedures and Forms Personnel Actions, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Faculty Personnel Committee Minutes and Notes, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Enrollment Data, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Budget Material, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Enrollment Data College of Arts and Science, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Faculty Personnel Committee, 1972 October 12 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - College of Arts Sciences Search Committee general folder, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - College Of Arts and Sciences Council, 1973-1974; 1974-1975; 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Executive Committee College of Arts and Sciences, 1972-1973; 1976 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - College of Arts and Sciences By-Laws, 1972 September 19 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - College of Arts and Sciences Executive Committee, 1973-1974; 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - College of Arts and Sciences Council, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Arts and Sciences Council Correspondence, 1974-1976 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Arts and Sciences Council Grievance, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Arts and Science Council, 1971-1972; 1968-1969; 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - College of Arts and Sciences By-Laws As Amended, 1973 October 1 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Preliminary Budget Requests, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Memo Deadlines For Promotion And Tenure Nominations, 1972 August 24 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Executive Committee College of Arts and Sciences, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Psychology Graduate Review, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Interdisciplinary Major Memos, 1972-1974 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Internal Evaluation Report Masters Degree in French PH.D In French, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Internal Evaluation of the M.S in Computer Science, 1972-1974 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - University Commitment To Full-Time Persons With Academic Rank, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - The status of Women At SUNY-Albany, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Transfer of Speech Pathology and Audiology, 1973 March-1973 April (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Transfer of Personnel From Chem, 1971-1972; 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Chairman Theatre, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Search Committees, 1972 June-1973 May (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Search Committee Speech Pathology Chairman, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Conferences With SIROTKIN, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Sociology Headship, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Student Evaluation of Teaching, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Regents Chairs, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Information on Research Grants, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Review of the general speech Program, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Review of Rhetoric and Communication Program, 1973 January 30 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Nominations and Elections, 1972 December 14 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Nuclear Accelerator, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Puerto Rican Studies, 1973-1975 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Reply to Carlos Perez, 1972-1974 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Proposed Merger of the Depths of Computer Science and Math, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Mail Log From, 1972 February 7-1972 November 14 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Chairman of Mathematics, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Master Plan SUNY, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Budget Summaries, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Review of Graduate Programs, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Biology Search Committee, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Associate Dean Div of Science and Math, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Meetings with Associate Deans, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - New York Archaeological Council, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Admissions Information, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - A+S Fac. Meeting, 1972 August 31 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Annual Report Division Science and Math, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Graduate Foreign Language Requirements, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - New Course Proposals, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - New Courses and Couse Changes, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Graduate Programs, 1955; 1960; 1962-1964 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - MA Programs, 1965 January (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Curriculum Comm, 1965-1966 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Curriculum Comm, 1965-1966 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Curriculum Comm, 1964-1965 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Podium West Extension, 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Experimental College, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Podium East Extension, 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Nursing School of, 1968-1970 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - School of Criminal Justice, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - PH.D Program Proposed, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Allocations Deans Office, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Commencement, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Reports Surveys Proposals, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Affirmative Action Women and Minorities, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - College Salaries Discretionary Raises For Faculty and NTPs, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Arts and Sciences Graduate Admissions, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Search Committees, 1972 April-1972 May (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Chairman Meetings, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Employment, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Doctoral Dissertations, 1970-1973 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Graduate Affairs Committee, 1970-1972 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Regionalization, 1972 June (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Classics Headship, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Womens Studies, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Annual Report, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Younger Humanist Fellowships, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Deans Council, 1971-1973 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Departmental Chairman APPTS, 1972 June 27 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Student Participation Humanities Department, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Urban Studies, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Variations in Summer School Grades, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Graduate Students Projections, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Grants and Contracts, 1973 May (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Guidelines For Self Study Documents, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Italo-American Studies, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Interdisciplinary Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - International Programs, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Israeli Program, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Professor Shunsuke Kamei, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Interdepartmental Studies Committee Actions Independent Study, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Deans Annual Report, 1971-1972; 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Curriculum Committee Action, 1970-1972 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Minutes, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Transmittal Memos, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Administrative Misc, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Agenda Memos, 1971-1973 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Faculty Personnel Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Committee on Academic Programs, 1972-1973; 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Committee on Academic Programs, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Committee on Academic Programs Proposals, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Executive Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - School and College By-Laws SUNY - Albany, 1973 October (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - College of Art and Sciences Faculty Roster, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Budget Reports, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Enrollment Data SUNYA, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Division of Humanities, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Division of Social and BEHAC SCI, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Division of Science Mathematics, 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Discretionary Salary Increments College of Arts and Sciences, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - C.A.P Proposals, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Divisional Faculty Rosters, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Faculty Personnel Committee and University Council, 1971-1973 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Meetings of Department Heads, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Meetings with Art Department, 1972 April 14 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Sirotkin Conferences, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Salary Inequities Women and Minorities, 1971-1973 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Faculty Lines, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Completed Recommendations For Promotion and Tenure, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Discretionary Salary Increments, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Humanities Budget, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Science and Mathematics Budget, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Social and Behavioral Sciences Budget, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Budget Memos, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Chairmans Meetings College of Arts and Sciences, 1972 June-1973 May (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Waiver of Non Employment Restriction While in PH.D Program, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Commitment to Geology, 1971-1974 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Council College Of Arts and Sciences, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Course Approval Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Chairmanship Comp, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Clinical Psychology Accreditation, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Academic Deans Retreat, 1973 March 23-1973 March 24 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Deans Meetings, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Discretionary Salary Increments, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Doctor of Arts Program, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Distinguished Teaching Professorship & Awards, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Economics Chairman, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Evaluation of Graduate Programs, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Evaluation of M.A in Afro American Studies, 1973 February 13 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Evaluation of M.A in Studio Art and M.A in Art History, 1973 February 13 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Evaluation of M.S in Atmospheric Science and Ph.D. in Atmospheric Science, 1973 May 16 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Evaluation of M.S in Astronomy and Ph.D. in Astronomy, 1973 February 13 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Evaluation of M.S in Computer Science, 1973 February 13 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Evaluation of M.A. in Economics M.A- Political Economy, 1973 February 14 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Evaluation of M/A in General Speech, 1973 April 19 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Evaluation of M.S. in Geology and Ph.D. in Geology, 1973 February 13 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Evaluation of PH.D. In Psychology, 1973 June 22 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Evaluation of M.A. in Social Studies, 1973 April 25 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Evaluation of M.S. in Speech Pathology and Audiology, 1973 February 13 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Evaluation of M.A Theatre, 1973 May 4 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Environmental Forum SUNYA, 1972 May 27 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Relocation of Geography Dept., 1972 August 7 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Equipment Requests From Science Depts, 1972 July (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Degree Candidates, 1972-1973; 1973 May 25 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Search Committee Environmental Studies, 1972 December 18 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - General File, 1973 January (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - General Information, 1972 November-1972 December (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - General Information, 1972 September-1972 October (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Proposed By-Laws, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - College of Arts & Sciences Curriculum Committee, 1966-1967 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - College of Arts and Sciences Curriculum Committee, 1966-1967 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Undergraduate Affairs Committee of Arts and Sciences, 1969-1970; 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - College of Arts and Sciences Curriculum Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - College of Arts and Sciences Curriculum Committee, 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Arts and Sciences College of, Asian Studies Committee, 1966-1973 September (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Arts and Sciences Asian Studies, 1973 October (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Memos Dept Chairmen Arts & Sciences, 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - College of Arts & Sciences Council, 1975 December 3 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - College of Arts & Sciences, 1975 May 5 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - College of Arts & Sciences, 1974 June 4 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - College of Arts & Sciences, 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Curriculum Committee Course Proposals, 1966 September-1967 May (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Curriculum Committee Course Proposals, 1966 September-1967 May (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Curriculum Committee Course Proposals, 1966 September-1967 May (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Curriculum Committee Course Proposals, 1967 November-1968 May (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Curriculum Committee Course Proposals, 1967 November-1968 May (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Curriculum Committee Course Proposals, 1967 November-1968 May (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - College Committee on EOP, 1968-1969 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Search Committee, 1973 July 27 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - College of Arts + Sciences, 1966-1971 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Committee Meeting Minutes, 1967-1974 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - New Material Search Committee, 1971 August 30 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Organization, 1971-1972; 1972 October 1 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Arts and Sciences Faculty Meetings, 1964-1971 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Arts and Sciences Faculty Meetings, 1968; 1971 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Arts and Sciences Council, 1964-1971 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Arts and Sciences, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - A&S Faculty Meetings, 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1966-1968 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Arts and Sciences Council, 1966-1968 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - A+S Undergraduate Academics Affairs Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Dear Search Committee External Candidates, 1970-1973 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Curriculum Committee of Arts and Sciences, 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Colmans Copies of Meeting Minutes, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Graduate Academic Council, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Letter File, 1976 July 26-1977 May 4 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Letter File, 1977 May-1977 September (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Letter File, 1975 May 3-1976 July 23 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Letter File, 1974 November 6-1975 June 30 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Letter File, 1974 March 4-1974 August 14 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Letter File, 1973 April 6-1974 March 4 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Letter File, 1972 August 16-1973 April 3 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Letter File, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Letter File, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Letter File, 1970 September-1971 January (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Letter File, 1971 January-1971 April (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Letter File, 1970 January-1970 May (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Letter File, 1970 May-1970 August (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Letter File, 1969 May-1969 August (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Letter File, 1969 August (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Department of English Self Study, 1971-1977 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Budget Summary Div of Hum, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Budget Worksheet, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Additional Needs, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Speech Activities Budget, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - FSA, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Budget, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Budget Materials, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Salary, 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Budget, 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Humanities, 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Humanities Building Room Assignments, 1969-1971 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Humanities Office Assignments, 1969-1971 (Box 9, Folder 5)